Contact

cathygilbert57@comcast.net

www.linkedin.com/in/cathy-gilbert-30754983 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Hospitals BLS

Honors-Awards

Nurse of the Year

Nurse Manager of the Quarter

Nurse Manager of The Quarter

Cathy Gilbert

Nurse Director 9/9S at Gadsden Regional Medical Center Gadsden, Alabama

Summary

I have 32 years experience as an RN.. I have 15 years of Labor and Delivery and Newborn nursery expertise. I worked both as a staff nurse and as a Nurse Manager in this area as well as Circulating OB cases. I recently managed a 27 Bed Medical Unit for 15 years and have House Supervision experience as well as Geri Psych. I am currently a Nurse Director of 9S/9 (Renal/Neuro/Dialysis)at GRMC. I am committed to nursing, It is my passion! I am a seasoned leader with expert leadership skills. I am loyal and dedicated to my career.

Experience

Gadsden Regional Medical Center

1 year

Nurse Director 9/9S August 2019 - Present (1 year) Gadsden, Alabama

Nurse Director 9/9S August 2019 - Present (1 year)

Department Director Renal and Stroke August 2019 - Present (1 year)

St Vincent's Health Nurse Manager June 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months) Pell City, Alabama

St. Vincents

Nurse Manager

June 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months)

St. Vincent's HealthCare Charge Nurse

December 2018 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Birmingham, Alabama Area

Charge Nurse-Medical Unit

Riverview Regional Medical Center

Nurse Manager

November 1996 - Present (23 years 9 months)

Supervise 35 associates, work in a management position. I work as a house supervisor as needed.

A very busy 27 bed medical unit, who specialize in Renal patients, and a New Vision detox program.

Staffing, budget, productivity, scheduling, patient satisfaction, quality and case management on a daily basis.

Regional Medical Center

RN

June 1987 - December 2013 (26 years 7 months)

Worked as a Labor and Deliver Staff Nurse during 1987-1996.presently works in a flexi role on postpartum as needed to keep my OB nursing up to date!!!

Gadsden Regional Medical Center

Staff RN

June 1990 - September 1996 (6 years 4 months)

Labor and Delivery Staff Nurse

UAB Medicine

RN

January 1995 - August 1995 (8 months)

High Risk OB

Education

Gadsden State Community College

Nursing, Nursing · (1984 - 1987)

Gadsden High School

High School Diploma, College Prep courses · (1972 - 1975)